A Guide to the Bolling Family Association Records, 1991-2009
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Bolling Family Association Records, 1991-2009
The Library of Virginia
51355
15.75 cubic feet (36 boxes).
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of the Bolling Family Association per S. Woodruff Bentley, Sr., Vienna.
Historical Information
The Bolling Family Association was founded in 1991 to collect, authenticate, analyze, and preserve information pertaining to the Bolling family or to any of its related families, such as Bowling, Bowlin, Bolin, Bolen, or Bolden. In addition, the Association collects all types of public and private, published and unpublished, family biographical and genealogical material, publishes newsletters, periodicals, publications, books, indexes, and other collected data, and distributes to libraries, historical societies, members, and interested organizations. The group also seeks to stimulate interest and provide oral and written guidance relative to historical and genealogical research. The BFA is also active in the restoration of homes, buildings, or structures associated with any families or groups in which it has an interest.
Scope and Content
Records, 1991-2009, of the Bolling Family Association, including lineage and miscellaneous files, and the papers of Association members Alexander R. "Bud" Bolling, Jr. (1922-2011) of Dallas, Texas; Chester T. Bolling (1925-2003) of Goochland County, Virginia; Joe E. Bowling (1932-2009) of Springdale, Arkansas; and Joseph Colin James, Jr. (1917-2010) of Denver, Colorado.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. Lineage Files.
Series II. Chester T. Bolling Files.
Series III. Colin James Files.
Series IV. Alexander R. Bolling, Jr. Files.
Series V. Joe E. Bowling Files.
Series VI. Miscellaneous Files.
Contents List
- Series I. Lineage Files., Extent: 12 boxes. (Box 1-12)
  The lineage files contain information provided by Association members that documents their Bolling ancestry, including family group sheets, pedigrees, descendancy charts, hereditary and patriotic organization applications, correspondence, genealogies, and published sources. Some of the material is contained on floppy discs. The information was entered into a lineage database maintained by the BFA. The files are organized alphabetically by member surname, and sometimes include the name of their Bolling ancestor and/or the member's state of residence.
  - Adams, Kelsey and Flora Bolling (Jeremiah Bolling 1782-1852) VA. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Adams, Marion Lee (James Bolling b. 1706). (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Agnew, Malcolm J. (Robert Bolling II) VA. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alderman, Daphna Lynette Bolen (Computer Disc) MI. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Allen, David and Magdalene Bowling (Benjamin Bowling b. 1807) AL. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Allen, Diana Dandridge (Dandridge/Spotswood/Tanner) OK. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Almquist, Thomas W. (Anne Bolling Hall b. 1713) CA. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Anderson, Barbara Boling (Eliot Bolling ca. 1770-1844) OK. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Anderson, Deborah (Robert Bolling m. Anne Cocke) TX. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Anderson, Frances M. (Matoaka Bolling b. 1729) SC. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Anderson, Karen (Sarah Ward) MD. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Anderson, Leslie A. and Sherri WA. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Andreas, Peggy Crego (Benjamin Bolling 1734-1832) NM. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Andrews, James T. and Nancy Spana (Martha Bolling Eldridge b. 1713) NC. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Anepohl, Ethel M. MS. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Angel, Leo S. and Wendy (Thomas Tabb Bolling 1762-1810) CA. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Antrim, John C. and Bonita Roe CA. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Armentrout, Louis A. (Nathaniel Bolen 1779-1870) OH. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Armstrong, Lynn W. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Bailey, Clifford G. and Artie Bolling (Benamin 1734-1832) VA. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Baker, M. Joeann P. (Jeremiah Bolling 1782-1853) KY. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Baldwin, Wayne F. (Nathaniel Bolen 1779-1870) VA. (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Barger, Nolan KY. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Barnickel, Irene G. (John Bolen - Brother of Elijah) OK. (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Bartell, Robert M. and Lanier H. (Jane Bolling Randolph 1703-1766) VA. (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Bartlett, Carol Hunt (William Elias Bowling b. 1717). (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Barwiniski, Ruby E. Hall (Bolling Green Hall 1838-1920) VA. (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Baughman, Virgil E. and Mary L. (Andrew Jackson Bowlin 1841-1904) OK. (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Beck, Marcia A. (Marinda Bolling) WA. (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Beckham, Mary (Texas Bowlings) NM. (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Beerbower, Randy and Lorelei (Benjamin Bolling 1734-1832) WA. (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Beeson, Dorothy Patton (Thomas Bowling 1580-1653) AZ. (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Beissell, Elmer A. and Elizabeth PA. (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Bentley, S. Woodruff (Elizabeth Bolling Gay 1709-1770). (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Berge, Linda (Edward Watson Bolling) VA. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Berry, Minnie Grace Bolen (Nathaniel Bolen 1779-1870) OH. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Blackmon, Richard C. and Joyce (John Bolling b. 1753) TX. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Blackwell, Claud and Elizabeth Hathcock (William Bolling 1731-1776) AL. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Blankinship, LaDonna J. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Bocetti, Billie (Benajamin Bolling b. 1734) NC. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Boland, Ernest. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Boland, William M. (Phillip Boland 1790-1831) MO. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Bolding, James Tarpley AR. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Bolen, R. Phillip (Edward Bolen 1785-1853) GA. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Bolen, Todd and Mary L. (Henry Bolen 1784-1864) IL. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Bolen, William L. and Eleanor (Nathaniel Bolen 1779-1870). (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Bolesta, Barb (Rachel S. Bolling b. ca. 1785) MO. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Bolen, E. J. Jr. (William Bowling b. 1828) KY. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Bolin, Edith TX. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Bolin, Elsie B. (Thomas Bolling 1766-1851) TN. (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Bolin, Martin Wright IN. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Bolin, Robert A. (George Bolin b. 1790) CA. (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Bolin, William Lee. (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Boling, Carolyn. (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Boling, Doyle Ray CA. (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Boling, Frederick and Wilma L. (John Boling) AR. (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Boling, George Benjamin Jr. TN. (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Boling, John Cochran Jr. (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Boling, John M. Jr. and Gwen (James Thomas Boling 1773-1838). (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Boling, Warren C. (John Boling b. ca. 1780). (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Boling, William D. (Charles D. Boling b. 1764) SC. (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Bolling, Alexander Russell Jr. (Robert Buckner Bolling 1805-1881). (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Bolling, Charles Jason Jr. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Bolling, Chester T. and Martha D. (Benjamin Bolling 1734-1832) VA. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Bolling, Earl W. (William Lemuel Bolling b. ca. 1810) TX. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Bolling, Glen Dale and Shirley Coomer (Jeremiah Bolling 1782-1852) MI. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Bolling, Lisa (James Bolin d. 1841) FL. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Bolling, Mrs. (Nasby) Margaret (Margaret Kathryn Bolling 1909-1947) CO. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Bolling, Roy Franklin and Patricia (Benjamin 1734-1832). (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Bolling, Samuel Blueford II. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Bolling, William P. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Bolling, Winston Blaker (William Bolling 1777-1848). (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Boshoven, Jack K. and Katherine (Jesse Bolling 1758-1841) CA. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Bouldin, Thomas W. (Thomas Bouldin b. 1706). (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Boowlin, Ann L. (George Bowlin 1801-1863) MO. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Bowlin, Clyde M. MO. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Bowlin, Debbi Jo (John Bowlin). (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Bowlin, Mike and Kathy. (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Bowlin, Paul F. and Dorothy M. (Benjamin Franklin Bowlin 1808-1874) CA. (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Bowlin, Robert D. (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Bowlin, Shari. (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Bowling, B. Carlisle and Elaine F. (James Bowling b. ca. 1775) FL. (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Bowling, Charles L. Jr. (Benjamin Bolling). (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Bowling, Daniel. (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Bowling, Donald Gene (Benjamin/Jeremiah Bolling) CO. (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Bowling, Ernest Clyde and Eunice (Jessie Bowling b. 1749) WV. (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Bowling, Ernest H. Jr. (James B. Bowling b. 1826). (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Bowling, Franklin Davis (William Bowling b. ca. 1701) NC. (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Bowling, G. John (John Bowling b. 1936) OH. (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Bowling, Garth Edward Jr. MD. (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Bowling, George E. (Jarrett Bowling 1761-1856) FL. (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Bowling, Harley KY. (Box 3, Folder 30-31)
  - Bowling, Hartwell (Riley Manning Bowling) MS. (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Bowling, Herbert C. and Dixie McCord (John Bowling 1741-1800) TX. (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Bowling, James H. (Thomas Bowling) OH. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Bowling, John Brooks (Martin Worthy Bowling b. 1821) AL. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Bowling, John Edelen (John Bowling ca. 1680-1711) MD. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Bowling, John Luther (Robert Bowling). (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Bowling, Larry D. and Dorothy W. (Alexander Bowling 1781-1843) PA. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Bowling, Larry Wayne. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Bowling, Marvin C. Jr. and Ann D. (Benjamin Bowling ca. 1704-1767) VA. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Bowling, Michael Frank (Delaney Bowlin 1774-1853). (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Bowling, Richard Hausber IV (Archibald Bolling 1831-1897) NC. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Bowling, Ruddell and Louise (Jesse Bolling 1758-1841) KY. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Bowling, Rudolph (Benjamin Bowling ca. 1706-1735). (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Bowling, Thomas Benson Sr. NC. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Bowling, W. Harry Jr. and Cecile A. (Jared Bowling 1732-1773). (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Bowling, William S. and Lori D. (William Bolling 1731-1776) VA. (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Bowling, Winston (James Bowling b. 1757). (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Bradshaw, Brenda Bolling (Luther W. Bowling 1904-1978) GA. (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Brady, Betty Vanderhoff FL. (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Brahin, R. Allen and Stephanie (Benjamin Bolling 1734-1832) VA. (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Brawley, Dorothy P. (Thomas Bolling 1735-1804) TN. (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Brewster, Eleanor (Edmond D. Bolling). (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Brigham, Marye (Richard Everard Meade 1778-1840). (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Brinkman, David E. and Deborah Root (James Bolling b. 1756) MI. (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Broaddus, Alice TX. (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Brogdon, Kathryn (Rachel C. Bolding). (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Browder, Barbara H. (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Brown, Bynum Rhodes (Elizabeth Bolling Munford b. 1709) NC. (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Brown, Charles H. and Mary Elizabeth (James Anderson Bowling) TN. (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Brown, Fola Keith (Jared Bolling 1732-1778) WV. (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Brown, Lee (Alexander Bolling b. 1721). (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Brown, Linda Carolyn (Benjamin Bolling 1734-1832) FL. (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Browning, David R. (William Bolling b. ca. 1776). (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Bryant, Ronald J. (Jean Bolling 1724-1795) IL. (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Burge, Nancy L.Hudson (Sims Bowling) MI. (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Burnett, David W. and Lynn M (Larkin Bowling). (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Burwitz, Phyllis Hudson (Benjamin Bolling 1734-1832) MN. (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Callahan, Sheila Dawn. (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Cantrell, James F. MO. (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Carr, Page (Sarah Bolling Tazewell) MD. (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Carter, Alma Lou Bolling. (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Cartwright, Betty Goff C. (Thornberry Bolling 1777-1837) TN. (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Cash, Mary-Margaret Parks. (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Casto, Terry Fay Smith (William Riley Bowling) TX. (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Chastain, Carol Ann Bowling (John Boling b. 1755) AL. (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Childs, Jack M. and Susan Bolen AR. (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Chronister, Ronald D. and Edna (Mitchell Boling 1827-1891) MI. (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Clayton, William TX. (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Cocks, Joel P. and Jacquelyn (John Bolling 1734-1800) VA. (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Collins, Hazel. (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Congdon, Dean and Jane (Martha Bolling 1713-1749) FL. (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Connell, Karl and Jean H. (Rachel Bowling b. 1810). (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Conway, Winnie (Pearl Bowling b. 1906 m. Oscar Hulen Ward). (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Cooley, Mildred Kimrey (James Tapley Bolling 1790-1877) VA. (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Coomer, B.G. "Bill" (Benjamin Bolling 1734-1832) IN. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Copeland, Thomas D. and Kay D. (Ann Bolling Dandridge b. 1752) TX. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Cornelius, Merl L. CA. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Cory, Marilee Howard (William Hall ca. 1730-1799) FL. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Crocker, Olva Bolling (Henry Clay Bowling). (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Cummings, Charles E. and Mary Elizabeth Bowling (Jeremiah Bolling Sr. 1782-1852) OH. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Cunningham, Sally Marsh (Elizabeth Bolling). (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Curran, Nan (Mary Ann Mays Bowlin). (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Cushman, Myrtie J.. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Dale, Ann Marie Fox (Benjamin Bolling 1734-1832) IN. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Dallas, Sioux Stallard Rutherford (Jeremiah Bolling 1782-1852) FL. (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Darnell, Alice (John Bolling 1737-1822) OK. (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Dartt, William H. Sr. and Evelyn Bolling Griffin (Alexander Bolling 1721-1766) NC. (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Davey, Howard (Benjamin Bolling 1734-1832). (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Davies, Hugh and Patricia (William Bolling b. 1777). (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Davis, Bruce G. and Mary J. (Thomas Bouldin of the Swan). (Box 5, Folder 16-22)
  - Davis, Darrel and Kay. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Davis, Elizabeth Vaughn (Milly Bolling Price m. John Harris Sr.) AL. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Davis, Joe and Bonnie (Albert Green Bowling 1852-1926) CA. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Davis, Sandra K. (Andrew L. Bolling 1783-1832) TX. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Davis, Wanda Bowlin (John Henry Franklin Bowling) TX. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Dawson, M. Jeanne "Jan" (John Bolling 1762-1822). (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Daykin, Shirley OK. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Dean, Jack P. and Elizabeth Tillman (Robert Bolling II) MS. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Denney, Bobby L. and Mary Anne CO. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Dennis, Margaret (John Layne Boling). (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Dittrich, John E. (William Bolling 1731-1776) TN. (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Dixon, Peggy Boling. (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Doerpers, Frankie Lee Bowling OH. (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Dondero, Janet Booker (Jane Bolling Randolph) MA. (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Dooley, Linda Bolling (Benjamin Bolling 1734-1832) OR. (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Doolittle, Trudy (Samuel Bolling) GA. (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Doyle, John B. and Joretta (Robert Bowlan b. 1782) TX. (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Duncan, Bruce C. (Thomas Bowling 1580-1655) OR. (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Dyer, L.L. and Viola I. WA. (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Eakes, Bennie A., Jr. (Charts For: Blackwell/Cagle/Cox/Eakes/Hancock/Wilkinson) NC. (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Ebert, James B. and Eleanor Lewis (John Bolling 1737-1822) NC. (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Edelen, Vivian (Thomas Bowling d. 1700). (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Elliott, A.R. and Lula Terry (Leanna Bolling 1770-1841) NM. (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Elmore, Betty Buchanan (Stith Bolling) DC. (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Elwin Line Article - August 1998 Newsletter. (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Emory, James Frederick (John Bolling 1769-1827). (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Farmer, J. Hoyt and Bolling Brown (William Bolling 1731-1776) GA. (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Faulkner, Jim D. and Cassandra L. (Henry Clay Bolling 1826-1904) NC. (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Fawcett, Helen (William Bolling 1731-1776) SC. (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Ferreira, Patty (Aaron Bowling m. Henrietta) OH. (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Ford, Danette Wiehl (Benjamin/Jesse Line) FL. (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Foster, Louise Scott VA. (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Foughty, Mada P. (Benjamin Bolling 1734-1832). (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Francis, Ben L. and Betty J. (Benjamin Bolling 1734-1832) CA. (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Franklin, Elise Bolling (Alexander Bolling 1721-1766) NC. (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Franklin, Lewis A. and Maureen (Benjamin Bolling 1734-1832) VA. (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Freeman, Al and Wanda (Sylvania Bowling 1867-1907) AZ. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Freeman, Ann Hayden (Martha Bolling m. Thomas Eldridge) CA. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Fryrear, Jack Ikard and Betty Jean Bowling (Nathaniel Bowling b. ca. 1823) OK. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Futch, Anne R. (Benjamin Bolling - Wise County) FL. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Gadberry, Morris and Betty (Jesse Bolling 1758-1841) OK. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Gano, Leonard and Dolores (Christopher Bolin 1787-1876) KS. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Garza, Toni (Elizabeth Bolling b. 1854) WA. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Geiser, Richard C. and Kimberly S. IL. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Gelineau, Shirley B. (Robert Bolling 1738-1775) TX. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Gellenbeck, Joyce Cunningham (Thomas Bowling 1759-1793) IN. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Geyer, Martha Stewart (Elizabeth Bowling m. Robert Mays) AL. (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Gibson, Charles K. and Louise A. (Ceatia Bowling Gibson b. 1875). (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Gibson, David and Sherry (Benjamin Bolling 1734-1832) TN. (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Gibson, Rev. Randy (Hannah Bolling Osborne b. 1763) NC. (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Gibson, Robert A. (Charles Walker Bowlin) OH. (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Giles, Dorothy Bowling (William Bowling m. Martha Jane Jefferson Meeks) VA. (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Gillenwater, Shirley L. (Benjamin Bolling 1734-1832) OH. (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Goodwin, David (Anne Clarke m. Robert Bolling) CA. (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Goodwin, Otis III and Elizabeth (John William Bowling 1735-1811) WA. (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Gordon, Jewell D. (Jesse Bolling 1758-1841) Canada. (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Gosink, Barbara B. (Thomas Bowling b. 1735 m. Sarah "Sally" Ford) CA. (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Gough, Leon H. and Judith Bowling (Thomas Bowling 1580-1653) MD. (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Grant, Mary Agnes. (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Gray, James Rodney (David Bowling). (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Green, William Jack and Naomi Hooper (Amelia "Millie" Bolling b. 1810) AK. (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Greif, Edward Earl (Col. Robert Bolling - 1660) KS. (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Griffin, Rodney (James Bolling m. Abagail McFee) KY. (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Grimes, Ella Vee (Hall Line) TX. (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Hales, Babs (Edward Bolling b. 1654) CA. (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Hall, Charles H. and Sylvia (Ann Bolling Hall 1713-1749) KY. (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Hall, Elke A. (Benjamin Bowling 1700-1767) VA. (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Hall, Gary (Hall Line) TX. (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Halstead-Johnson, Adria (Benjamin Bowling b. 1732 m. Winifred Garrison) VT. (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Ham, Donald E. and Dolores Ramsey (Elizabeth Bowling Speake) SC. (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Haney, Stephen F. Jr. and Sarah Bowling Williams (Robert Leroy Bowling 1823-1887) FL. (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Hanson, James H. (Nancy Bowling m. Lemuel Wilkerson) MN. (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Harness, Linda. (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Harris, Ralph and June (Sarah Bolling Megginson) VA. (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Harrison, Louie Walden Sr. and Doris Stoner Harrison (Benjamin Bolling/Cagle Lines) TX. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Hartline, Roger D. and Morgan R. (Penelope Bolling Clark) LA. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Harwell, Walter Robert (Susan Bolling Stewart) FL. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Hayes, James F. and Barbara King (George F. Bolen 1832-1877) FL. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Haygood, Katherine (Anne Bolling b. 1718 m. James Murray). (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Hayman, Bill TN. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Heisel, John and Vella M. (Benjamin Bolling 1734-1832). (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Heiss, Joyce Sheckler TN. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Helm, June Boling (William H. Boling b. 1932). (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Henderson, R.P. and Margaret R. Bolling (William Bolling 1731-1776) FL. (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Hermanson, Mattie L. (Benjamin Bolling 1734-1832) WA. (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Hess, Mary Amis Bowling (Benjamin Bolling 1734-1832) OH. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Heywood, Myrtle B. UT. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Hicks, Kenneth and Nancy (Joseph Berry Bowling 1849-1896) TN. (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Hine, Leighton L. and Patricia M. (Jesse Bowling 1758-1841) OH. (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Hipp, Mary Kathryn Bowlin (Andrew Lucius Bowling 1783-1832) TX. (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Hobbs, T. Gibson Jr. and Peggy (Robert Buckner Bolling 1805-1881) VA. (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Hodge, Charles C. and Mary Jo (John William Bowling 1856-1918) NY. (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Holder, Janet (William Bolling 1731-1776) VA. (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Holland, Martha Gholson TX. (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Holland, Sarah Bowling (William Bowling 1789-1855) FL. (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Hopson, Rex C. (Alexander Bolling 1721-1767) NE. (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Hosack, Vernona M. MI. (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Hounshell, Warnie and Ephtha (Jeremiah Bolling 1782-1852) VA. (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - House, Wiley J. and Betty (Rodney Bowlin) CA. (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Howard, William T. Jr. and Bess (Jane Bolling Randolph 1703-1766) MD. (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Hubler, Parley and Nettie Boling (Benjamin Bolling 1734-1832) OK. (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Hudgins, William D. and Rebecca Beau Allen (Elliott Bolling 1765-1844) NC. (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Hunt, Patricia Ann Burkett (Morris Bolling - Rolfe Line). (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Hutton, Ernest W. and Vera Bowling (James Bowling 1811-1892) VA. (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Irvin, Bill C. and Faye (Nancy Bolling Allen) FL. (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Jaggears, Kenneth B. and Helen P. (Manning Bowling ca. 1777-1816) AL. (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - James, Colin CO. (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Jeffries, John T. Sr. and Linda Bolen (Benjamin Bolling 1734-1832) OH. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Jenkins, Charles F. and Agnes Bowers (Agnes Bolling Kennon 1700-1765) OH. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Johnson, James A. Sr. (Lucinda Bolling b. ca. 1792) FL. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Johnson, Minnie Yancey (Mary Bolling Yancey 1711-1795) TX. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Jones, Boyd L. (Lucinda Bowling Howard b. 1814) TX. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Jones, Dorothy Bolling (John Henry Bolling AL/TX) TN. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Jones, Raymond K. and Sandra Lee (James Butler Bowling 1795-1878). (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Keaton, Herman Jr. (Bollen-Bolden-Danforth-Morris) GA. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Keller, Maria G. (William Bowling 1789-1855) VA. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Kesler, Charles H. and Juanita J. (Sarah Bolling Snead) NC. (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Kiser, Doris Harman. (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Kitoo, Jeffrey David (Benjamin Bolling) CA. (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Klein, Ruth Estridge. (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Knowles, Brantley C. (Thomas Bolling) VA. (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Knowles, Robert W. and Delores J. (James Bolling b. 1756) VA. (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Koo, Rachal S. (Jesse Bowling m. Susan S. Robertson) WV. (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Kotliar, Jay (Robert Bolling 1646-1709). (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Krodell, Carolyn Bates (Jarrett Bolling 1762-1856) AR. (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Kuster, Arthur and Dolores (Edmund Bolling 1760-1834). (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Lambeth, Robert Bolling Jr. and Lynn Beebe (Robert Buckner Bolling 1805-1881) VA. (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Lattin, Larry and Joanne (Tapley Bolling 1790-1877) IN. (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Lawrence, James Reed Jr. and Verlee Bolling (Francis Bolling m. Hannah Dean) KY. (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Lazarre, Mark M. (John Bolling b. ca. 1765) LA. (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Lee, Sally C. (Evelyn Bolling Cox b. 1927). (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Lentz, Norma Bowling (William R. Bolling) NC. (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Lesesne, Louis LeMaire Jr. and Tamara Pryor Smith (Jean Elizabeth Bolling m. Miller Bledsoe). (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Lillibridge, John L. and Audrey R. (Benjamin Bolling 1734-1832) FL. (Box 9, Folder 27)